How much is your family worth?
Extortion is a action, adventure, crime film directed by Phil Volken.
A doctor desperately tries to save his wife and their 5 year old son after
their vacation in the Bahamas takes an unexpected turn.
Julie Riley, played by Bethany Joy Lenz.
Constable Haagen, played by Danny Glover.
Actor, played by Tim Griffin.
Kevin Riley, played by Eion Bailey.
Miguel Kaba, played by Barkhad Abdi.
Lucas, played by Jack Wallace.
Extortion, is a 2017 American thriller film, starring Eion Bailey,
Bethany Joy Lenz, Barkhad Abdi, and Danny Glover.
The film explores themes of kidnapping, bahamas, extortion, family vacation.
The tone is emotional and intense.